Warren Roche

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Details

+4915730675425

warrengamedev@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH

28/11/92

Links

Portfolio

Linkedin

Github

Skills

Angular

Springboot

Quarkus

Java

Typescript and Javascript

SQL and Postgresql

Payara/Glassfish

Jenkins

Bootstrap Tailwind Ionic Material

Unity

C#

Postgres and oracle DB

NPM

Maven

HTML5 CSS SCSS/SASS

JUnit Mockito

Git Github Bitbucket Confluence Jira ITSM

Hibernate and JPA

Client side and server side rendering

SOLID and object-oriented design

Languages

English

German

Profile

Hi, my name is Warren and I work as a full stack web developer in

Munich. I have a MSc from the Technical University of Dublin specializing in game development, and a BA in German and English from Maynooth University. If you would like to discuss anything regarding my experience or projects, feel free to reach out

Employment History

Full Stack Software Developer, Adesso SE, Munich

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

- Worked as solo full stack developer on two web applications for a large client in the automotive industry.
- Planned, designed, developed and deployed new features together with the client
- Successfully migrated Angular frontends to latest major versions.
- Maintained and improved the CI/CD pipeline.
- Developed and deployed software in an agile environment.
- Analysed and resolved defects.
- Wrote clean, flexible, readable, unit tested code in the fronted and backend.
- Refactored legacy code to be cleaner and more performant.
- Implemented Restful web services using JDBC.
- Liaised with the client and many other departments as needed.

Full Stack Software Developer, Akka, Munich

APRIL 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- Developed feature sets for an internationally used cross-platform web application using Angular, Typescript, SCSS/SASS, Ionic, and Xcode.
- Developed features sets for a large scale web portal using Liferay, Java EE, JSP, Javascript, Typescript, CSS, Oracle SQL, Docker, and WSL.
- Liaised closely with the client when refining, developing, and delivering new feature sets.
- Facilitated knowledge transfer between team members.
- Onboarded new team members.
- Worked in pair programming sessions.

Education

MSc Creative Digital Media, specialization: game development, Technological University Dublin, Dublin

SEPTEMBER 2017 - FEBRUARY 2019

BA English and German, Maynooth University, Maynooth

SEPTEMBER 2011 - MAY 2015

Additional first year subject: Psychology

References

References available upon request